<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Saku-Movie™️</string>
    <string name="movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="max_rating">/ 10</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="release_on">Release on :</string>
    <string-array name="title">
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bird Box</item>
        <item>Once Upon a Dead Pool</item>
        <item>How to Train Your Dragon : Hidden World</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball Super: Broly</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="description">
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one
            hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy,
            his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his
            twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate
            of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two
            children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>
        <item>A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpool’s PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2 as a Princess Bride-esque
            story that’s full of magic, wonder and zero F’s.</item>
        <item>As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless’ discovery of an untamed,
            elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup’s reign as village chief is
            tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.</item>
        <item>As Goku investigates the destruction of the Southern Galaxy, Vegeta is taken to be King of the New Planet
            Vegeta, and to destroy the Legendary Super Saiyan, Broly.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="release_date">
        <item>2018–04–25</item>
        <item>2018–12–13</item>
        <item>2018–12–11</item>
        <item>2019–01–03</item>
        <item>2018–12–14</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rating">
        <item>8.3</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>7.7</item>
        <item>7.4</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="image">
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
